I know that it comes from a good place. But when y'all say things to me, like,
I hope, damn, I can't just scratch the shit out of me. I hope you're not spending all day
consuming this. It's like, what y'all, there's 24 hours in the day. There's 24 hours in the day.
And also, I just want to say, like, even if I was, so the fuck what? Like, I don't know what
this obsession is with, like, making sure that we're comfortable. But, you know, there's a real
thing happening right now. Like, a real fucking thing is, like, actually happening. And so if we
are immersed in it, and we are continuously paying attention to it, you know, there's this, like,
American privilege of, like, you know, make sure you step away, make sure you take care of yourself.
And it's like, I think that what you have to learn how to do is to take care of yourself in
the midst of it. You know, like, I mean, maybe that's what you all mean, but it doesn't come
off that way. You know, like, our civil rights leaders, and let's be real, beyond the civil
rights leaders, like, Black people in America, until maybe, like, the 80s, were 70s, 60s, because
the 60s was a time, were constantly living under threat of violence, were constantly
living within the confines of an apartheid state. They didn't get to step away. They had
to figure out how to still find joy, how to still find pockets of peace, how to still find,
you know, love, ambition, all of these things within. You don't get to step away.
And for the record, even when you do step away, it's still on your mind, because it doesn't go
away just because you stepped away. I guess what I'm saying is that when consciousness is raised
truly, right, it is not merely a side piece to your state of being. No, in order for it to
truly be acknowledged and effective, it has to become a part of your state of being.
And your state of being changes. It is raising your vibration. That's what's happening.
Let me let this dog go to the bathroom.